<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>professionalresponsibility on Chris Wingard</title><link>/tags/professionalresponsibility/</link><description>Recent content in professionalresponsibility on Chris Wingard</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/professionalresponsibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Climate Change Policy Action</title><link>/blog/climate-_change_policy_action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/climate-_change_policy_action/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Since there is such scientific uncertainty about global warming, it is unreasonable to take any drastic policy steps. Do you agree?&amp;rdquo;
It is unreasonable to suggest that there is significant scientific uncertainty surrounding global warming. Consequently, it would be nothing short of reckless for humanity to refuse to implement drastic policy changes to address the causal relationship between our actions and the Earth&amp;rsquo;s changing climate. When asked what is the most pressing challenge facing the United States, presidential candidate Bernie Sanders coolly replied climate change.</description></item><item><title>Climate Risks and Cape Cod:</title><link>/blog/climate_risks_cape_cod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/climate_risks_cape_cod/</guid><description>Climate Risks and Cape Cod:
How State, County, and Local Governments Respond to a Crisis
Climate change poses an existential threat to coastal communities around the world. New England is home to one such community: Cape Cod, a peninsula with 560 miles of coastline extending into the Atlantic from mainland Massachusetts.1 Surrounded by water on all sides and with a max elevation of only three hundred and six feet, the Cape is acutely vulnerable to sea level rise and other climate risks.</description></item></channel></rss>