<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Wingard</title>
    <link>https://chriswingard.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Wingard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chriswingard.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Bar Exam Should be Abolished</title>
      <link>https://chriswingard.com/blog/bar_exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriswingard.com/blog/bar_exam/</guid>
      <description>As the Spring semester draws to a close, thousands of soon-to-be law school graduates across the country will shift their attention to the final hurdle to become a lawyer: the bar exam. Unfortunately, this ultimate barrier to practice is designed to arbitrarily exclude qualified individuals from the profession, bears no rational relationship to the actual practice of law, and is harmful to consumers. The bar exam should be abolished because it would increase access to the profession, decrease legal costs for consumers, and have little to no adverse effect on the quality of legal services provided by the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chriswingard.com/featurette/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriswingard.com/featurette/</guid>
      <description>Homepage type: widget_page
Homepage is headless, other widget pages are not. headless: true</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chriswingard.com/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriswingard.com/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Chris Wingard</title>
      <link>https://chriswingard.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriswingard.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I received my JD/MBA with Honors from Boston University and now work as an Associate at Morgan Lewis. I&amp;rsquo;m admitted to practice law in Massachusetts and Pennsylvania.
Previously, I studied at Pembroke College, Oxford University and Tufts University, where I graduated summa cum laude with a double major in Economics and Environmental Studies. I was also selected a Tufts Senior Award Winner and inducted into the Phi Betta Kappa honors society.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
